https://permanentmakeup.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
When accessing our website, we will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site.
Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, our company has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting our website, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail or filling out a contact form containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message. Such information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.
Links to third party Websites
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of our company then you may contact us.
Contact Us
Like Us on Facebook
Contact
Missoula
406.370.3705
1821 South Ave W, Suite 404
Missoula, Montana 59801
Bozeman
Hours:
By Appointment Only
Leave a Review
Copyright © 2020 Privacy Policy | Design by: Big West Marketing
